A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appointments Office, 1959-1965; 1; 9 Cubic Feet
  - Regrets, January 1964 (Box 16, Folder 500)
    1. Federation of Jewish Philanthropies 2. New York Couture Group
  - Albany, New York, February 3, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 501)
  - Albany, New York, February 4, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 502)
    1. New York State Sheriff's Association 2. Empire State Chamber of Commerce
  - New York, New York, February 5, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 503)
    1. "Rockefeller for President" National Campaign Headquarters Opening 2. The Bond Club of New York
  - Washington, DC, February 6, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 504)
    1. Chamber of Commerce of the United States 2. "Rockefeller for President Committee" Headquarters Opening
  - Oregon, February 7-8, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 505)
    February 7 1. Portland - Press conference 2. Portland - Rockefeller Headquarters Opening 3. Portland - Luncheon 4. Medford - Press conference 5. Medford - Lincoln Day Banquet February 8 1. Roseburg - Airport reception 2. Roseburg - Reception and luncheon 3. Salem - "Students for Rockefeller" 4. Executive Committee of the Jaycees
  - New York, New York, February 11, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 506)
    1. Association of Towns Banquet 2. Association of Fire Districts, New York State
  - New Hampshire, February 12-14, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 507)
    February 12 1. Dover - Tour 2. Rye - Coffee at Town Hall 3. Northwood - Tea at Elementary School 4. Concord - Delegate Meeting February 13 1. Daytime tours of Hopkinton, Contoocook, Kingsbury, Warner, Bradford, Newbury(lunch), Sunapee, Dorr Woolen Co., Newport 2. Claremont - Annual Awards Night, Claremont Junior Chamber of Commerce February 14 1. Daytime tours of Hanover (lunch), Canaan, Lyme, Orford, Enfield, Piermont, North Haverhill, and Woodsville 2. Dinner in Lower Town Hall, Lebanon 3. Tour of Main Street, Lebanon
  - New York, New York, February 16, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 508)
    1. WABC-TV taping of "Issues and Answers"
  - Albany, New York, February 18, 1964; New Hampshire, February 19-23, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 509)
    Albany 1. Board of Associated Industries of New York State 2. American Jewish Congress 3. Legislative Correspondents Association 4. Legislative Dinner for War Veterans New Hampshire - February 19 1. Appearances in Rochester, Stratham, Exeter, Kingston, Salem New Hampshire - February 20 1. Appearances in Manchester, Bedford, Goffstown 2. Manchester - Dinner and public meeting February 21 - New Hampshire 1. Appearances in Boscawen, Franklin, Bristol, Plymouth, North Woodstock, Cannon Mountain, Franconia Notch, Franconia, Littleton February 22 - New Hampshire 1. Appearances in Whitefield, Groveton, Lancaster, Gorham, Berlin February 23 - New Hampshire 1. Appearances in North Conway, Center Harbor, Merideth 2. Laconia - Dog sled races, coffee
  - Albany, New York, February 24, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 510)
    1. New York State Federation of Republican Women 2. New York State League of Women Voters 3. New York State Council of Churches
  - New York, New York; Vermont, February 27, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 511)
    New York City 1. Delaware River Basin Commission Vermont 1. Burlington - University of Vermont 2. Burlington - Call on Mrs. Warren Austin 3. Burlington - Coffee Hour, Hotel Burlington 4. Montpelier - "Vermonters for Rockefeller" 5. Montpelier - Dinner with campaign workers
  - New Hampshire, February 28-29, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 512)
    February 28 1. Tours of Marlboro, Dublin, Jaffrey, Fitzwilliam, Winchester 2. Keene a. Miniature Precision Plant b. Peerless Insurance Company c. Markem Machine Plant d. Dinner e. Business District Tour f. Public Campaign Reception February 29 1. Tours of North Conway, Conway, Chocorua, West Ossipee, Center Harbor, Merideth, Weirs, Lakeport, Laconia
  - Regrets, February 1964 (Box 16, Folder 513)
    1. Chicago Conference for Brotherhood 2. Association of Industrial Advertisers 3. Rochester Federation of Women's Clubs 4. Public Affairs Club, Harvard Business School 5. American Fraternal Zionist Organization 6. American Society of Travel Agents 7. Broome County Lincoln Day Dinner 8. Gore Mountain Ski Center Dedication
  - New Hampshire, March 4-9, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 514)
    March 4 1. Tour of Concord 2. Henniker - New England College Convocation 3. Concord - Rally March 5 1. Tour of Concord area 2. Tour of Durham 3. Durham - University of New Hampshire 4. Tour of Dover and Portsmouth area March 6 1. Tour of Seabrook and Rochester area 2. Tour of Hampton and Plaistow area 3. Hudson - Rally March 7 1. Nashua - Breakfast 2. Tour of Hollis and Amherst area 3. Manchester - Supper and rally March 8 1. WMUR-TV, "Face the Nation" appearance 2. Tour of Manchester area March 9 1. Manchester - Meeting of joint service clubs
  - California, March 11-14, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 515)
    March 11 1. Sacramento - Legislator's luncheon 2. Sacramento - Press conference 3. Sacramento - Rockefeller leadership meeting 4. Concord - Chamber of Commerce Dinner March 12 1. Oakland-Bay Area Negroes Community Breakfast 2. Berkeley - University of California a. Visit with Chancellor b. Formal address to students 3. Granada Hills - Knollwood Country Club March 13 1. Breakfast with Rockefeller leadership 2. University of Southern California a. Press conference b. Meeting with University of Southern California President and Chancellor c. Brunch with trustees and faculty d. Address University of Southern California students 3. Fresno - Republican County Committee 4. Fresno - Press conference 5. Fresno - Reception March 14 1. California Republican Assembly Convention
  - New York, New York, March 12, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 516)
    1. United Jewish Appeal Dinner (regret)
  - Albany, New York, March 14, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 517)
    1. Legislative Correspondents Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 16, 1964; New York, New York, March 17, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 518)
    Albany 1. Department of Public Works, Technical Services Subdivision New York City 1. St. Patrick's Day Parade (regret)
  - Washington, DC, March 18, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 519)
    1. Reception at the Chilean Embassy
  - Oregon and California, March 30-April 3, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 520)
    March 30 - Oregon 1. Ontario - Chamber of Commerce breakfast 2. Ontario - High School 3. LaGrande - Eastern Oregon College 4. Pendleton - Vert Auditorium rally 5. The Dalles - Reception 6. Bend - Community College March 31 - Oregon 1. Eugene - Press conference 2. Eugene - Opening of Rockefeller Headquarters 3. Eugene - Lane County Fairgrounds 4. Portland - KOIN-TV, statewide telethon April 1 - San Francisco 1. Rockefeller Steering Committee luncheon 2. "Spectrum 74," radio show taping 3. Stanford University address 4. Reception April 2 - Los Angeles 1. University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) a. Press conference b. Meeting with Chancellor c. Address to students d. Reception and lunch 2. ABC-TV taping of Retail Clerks program 3. Reception April 3 - Los Angeles 1. Leadership breakfast 2. Luncheon with Rockefeller workers 3. Tour of North American Aviation Plant
  - Regrets, March 1964 (Box 16, Folder 521)
    1. Taping request 2. "Meet the Press" request 3. Home Manufacturers Association 4. Lewisboro Republican Club 5. Williamsburg General Hospital
  - NOT USED (Box 16, Folder 522)
  - New York, New York, April 7, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 523)
    1. Memorial Service for General Douglas MacArthur
  - Baltimore, Maryland, April 8, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 524)
    1. Johns Hopkins University 2. Reception, Sutton Place
  - Washington, DC, April 9, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 525)
    1. Women's National Press Club 2. Republican Women's Conference 3. Reception, Sheraton Park Hotel
  - Washington, DC, April 10, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 526)
    1. Republican National Finance Committee (canceled)
  - Oregon (original itinerary, not used), April 15-18, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 527)
  - Oregon, California, Louisiana, April 17-21, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 528)
    April 17 - Oregon 1. Corvallis - Oregon State University 2. Portland - City Club of Portland 3. Gresham - Chamber of Commerce 4. Portland - Mock Convention April 20 - San Diego, California 1. Rockefeller leadership breakfast 2. Press conference 3. Kiwanis Club Luncheon 4. Television taping 5. Reception and meeting with local press April 21 - New Orleans, Louisiana 1. Pan-American Seminar Luncheon
  - New York, New York, April 19, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 529)
    1. Directors of the Associated Press 2. Dedication of Vatican Pavilion (canceled)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, April 21, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 530)
    1. Pan-American Seminar Luncheon
  - New York, New York, April 22-23, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 531)
    April 22 1. Official Opening of New York World's Fair April 23 1. New York State Day at World's Fair Schedules for New York Days at World's Fair
  - Oregon, California, April 27-29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 532)
    April 27 - Oregon 1. Winema - Speech 2. Grants Pass - Rockefeller Committee Luncheon 3. Albany - Chamber of Commerce reception 4. Portland - Lloyd Center Shopping Center April 28 - California 1. Sacramento - Press Club and California Newspaper Publisher Association 2. Sacramento - Meeting, "Sacramento Bee" Editors 3. Burbank - Airport reception 4. Pasadena - Private reception 5. Pasadena - Civic Auditorium reception April 29 - Los Angeles 1. KGBS-radio interview taping 2. KABC-TV taping, "770 on TV," Retail Clerks Union Show 3. Republican Associated Luncheon 4. Mexican American Steering Committee 5. Receptions
  - West Virginia, April 30-May 1, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 533)
    April 30 1. Bluefield - Breakfast with local leaders 2. Welch - Tour, receptions 3. Raleigh County Armory - Luncheon 4. Charleston - WCHS-TV taping 5. Charleston - Press conference and reception May 1 1. Parkersburg - Breakfast with local leaders 2. Wheeling - Bethany College Forum 3. Clarksburg - Rally 4. Morgan - Reception, Law Day ceremony
  - Regrets, April 1964 (Box 17, Folder 534)
    1. Law Day Observance - Albany, New York 2. Nassau County Republican Committee
  - New York, New York, May 4, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 535)
    1. Jubilee Dinner for Cardinal Spellman
  - New York, New York, May 6, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 536)
  - Chicago, Illinois, May 7, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 537)
    1. Executive club Luncheon 2. Meeting with Republican Leaders 3. Taped TV interview
  - Oregon, California, May 8-14, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 538)
    May 8 - Oregon 1. Astoria - Breakfast 2. Tillamook - Rockefeller for President Headquarters Opening 3. Salem - Public Luncheon 4. Dallas - Reception 5. Eugene - University of Oregon public meeting May 11 - Oregon 1. Hillsboro - Masonic Lodge reception 2. Beaverton - Tektronix Plant tour 3. Riviera Motors - Handshaking 4. Raleigh Hills - Shopping Center 5. Beaverton - Handshaking, luncheon 6. Milwaukie - Omark Industries 7. Milwaukie - Omard Fastening Plant 8. Milwaukie - Elks Club reception 9. Oregon City - Shopping Center 10. Oregon City - Rockefeller for President Headquarters 11. Oregon City - Law Day Dinner May 12 - Oregon 1. Newport - Rockefeller for President Headquarters 2. Coos Bay - Rotary Club luncheon 3. Portland - Statewide one hour telethon May 13 1. Arcata, California - Humboldt State College 2. Portland, Oregon - University of Portland May 14 - Oregon 1. McMinnville - Chamber of Commerce breakfast 2. McMinnville - Cascade Footwear site 3. Portland - Eagles Lodge
  - New York, New York, May 18, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 539)
    1. Michigan Day at New York World's Fair
  - California, May 19-29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 540)
    May 19 1. Los Angeles - Press conference 2. Northridge - San Fernando State College 3. Los Angeles - Television hook-up May 20 1. Riverside County - California Baptist College 2. San Bernardino Valley College a. Presentation and discussion b. Television taping 3. Orange Show Fairgrounds - Luncheon 4. Disneyland Hotel May 21 1. "Puddle Jump" on plane to Bakersfield, Fresno 2. Stockton - University of the Pacific 3. Oakland - Reception May 22 1. Breakfast with Bay Area Republican Alliance 2. Press conference 3. Luncheon with Labor Leaders 4. Television and radio appearances May 25 1. San Diego - KFMB-TV taping 2. San Diego - KOGO-TV, "The Regis Philbin Show" 3. San Diego - Press conference 4. San Diego - Motorcade 5. San Diego - State College, address 6. Los Angeles - KMEX-TV taping (in Spanish) 7. Long Beach - Elks Club reception, address May 26 1. Ventura - Rockefeller for President Headquarters 2. Santa Barbara - Channel City Club 3. Burbank - NBC-TV studio taping 4. Beverly Hills - Rockefeller for President Headquarters, rally May 27 - Los Angeles 1. Hollywood - KTLA-TV taping 2. Warner Brothers Studios luncheon 3. Loyola University address May 28 1. Monterey County Fairgrounds Reception, rally 2. Santa Cruz - Reception 3. Santa Clara Fairgrounds reception May 29 - San Francisco 1. Commonwealth Club address
  - Regrets, May 1964 (Box 17, Folder 541)
    1. City of New Rochelle 2. National AAU Judo Championships 3. Suffolk County Republican Committee 4. Republican State Central Committee (Illinois) 5. New York State Jaycee Convention 6. New York State Junior Chamber of Commerce
  - Suffolk County, New York, June 4, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 542)
    1. Suffolk County Republican Committee
  - Cleveland, Ohio, June 7-9, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 543)
    1. Republican Governor's Conference
  - Albany, New York, June 11, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 544)
    1. New York State Republican Committee
  - New York, New York; Lido Beach, New York, June 25, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 545)
    New York City 1. United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York Lido Beach 1. Joseph P. Carlino Scholarship Dinner
  - Saratoga, New York, June 25, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 546)
    1. Saratoga Performing Arts Center (SPAC) ground breaking
  - Regrets, June 1964 (Box 17, Folder 547)
    1. Meeting with New Jersey Delegation 2. New York State Commission on Human Rights 3. National Editorial Association 4. Ludlow Community Association 5. Trinity Cathedral - Cleveland, Ohio 6. National Forum on Ethics 7. Sons of Italy in America
  - San Francisco, California, July 13-17, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 548)
  - NOT USED (Box 17, Folder 549)
  - Regrets, July 1964 (Box 18, Folder 550)
    1. Press Club of San Francisco 2. Long Island Arts Center Opening 3. National Association of Secretaries of State
  - Syracuse, New York; New York, New York, August 4-5, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 551)
    August 4 - Syracuse 1. Syracuse University reception August 5 - Syracuse 1. Dedication, Samuel I. Newhouse Communications Center at Syracuse University August 5 - New York City 1. Conference of the Chief Justices of the United States
  - Albany, New York, August 6, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 552)
    1. New York State Republican Chairmen
  - New York, New York, August 10, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 553)
    1. American Bar Association
  - Hershey, Pennsylvania, August 12, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 554)
  - Niagara Falls, New York, August 21, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 555)
  - New York, New York, August 31, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 556)
  - Regrets, August 1964 (Box 18, Folder 557)
    1. Federation of Insurance Counsel 2. Candidates Conference 3. Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity 4. Monroe County Fair
  - Syracuse, New York, September 2-3, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 558)
    1. New York State Fair and Exposition
  - New York, New York, September 4, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 559)
    1. Inter-American Rural Youth Leaders Conference
  - Brooklyn, New York, September 15, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 560)
    1. Republican Headquarters Opening
  - New York, New York, September 17, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 561)
    1. New York State Board of Social Welfare
  - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 21, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 562)
    1. County Officers Association of New York State
  - Albany, New York; Saranac Lake, New York, September 25, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 563)
    Albany 1. Meeting and rally with Senator Barry Goldwater Saranac Lake 1. Associated Industries of New York State
  - New York, New York, September 26, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 564)
    1. National Legislative Leaders Conference 2. Steuben Parade
  - Syracuse, New York, September 30, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 565)
    1. Syracuse and Central New York Chambers of Commerce and Trade Associations
  - Regrets, September 1964 (Box 18, Folder 566)
    1. Westchester County Day 2. Ogden Reid's Reelection Headquarters Opening 3. Tupper Lake 4. Albany County Fund Raising Dinner 5. Chemung County Republican Picnic 6. Candidates Assistance Meeting (Oregon) 7. Association of Young Republican Clubs 8. New York State Employees Council, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) 9. Sullivan County Hotel Association 10. Sons of Italy Day, New York World's Fair
  - New York, New York, October 4, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 567)
    1. Pulaski Day Parade 2. Madison Square Garden Rally
  - New York, New York, October 5, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 568)
    1. Meeting with Judicial Districts of New York State
  - New York State, October 6, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 569)
    1. Buffalo - 8th Judicial District 2. Rochester - 7th Judicial District 3. Syracuse - 5th and 6th Judicial Districts 4. Albany - 3rd and 4th Judicial Districts
  - New York, New York, October 7, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 570)
    1. Reception for Congressman John Lindsay
  - Westchester County, New York, October 8, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 571)
    (NAR campaigning for Senator Ken Keating) 1. Eastchester - Republican Women Coffee Hour 2. Pleasantville - General Precision Labs 3. Pleasantville - Readers Digest 4. Briarcliff Manor - Briarcliff College 5. Elmsford - Master's Shopping Center 6. North Tarrytown - General Motors Plant 7. North Tarrytown - Fisher Body Plant 8. Tarrytown - Marymount College 9. White Plains - Keating Headquarters 10. Tarrytown - Scarsdale Town Republican Committee Dinner
  - New York, New York, October 9, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 572)
    1. American Public Health Association 2. Two political rallies (for Senator Ken Keating) 3. Division of Housing and Community Renewal
  - New York, New York, October 12, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 573)
    1. Columbus Day Parade (reviewing stand)
  - New York, New York, October 14, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 574)
    1. Airport Operators Council 2. Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner
  - New York, New York, October 15, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 575)
    1. Committee on the Education and Employment of Women 2. Urban League of Greater New York
  - New York, New York, October 16, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 576)
    1. New York World's Fair
  - New York, New York, October 19, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 577)
    1. Federation of Women's Republican Clubs (hosted by Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller)
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 20, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 578)
    1. Oneonta - Elks Club luncheon 2. Cobleskill - Reception 3. Schenectady - Dinner with Republican leaders 4. Schenectady - Rally, Hellenic Center
  - New York, New York, October 22, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 579)
    1. Funeral Services for President Herbert Hoover
  - Chautauqua County, New York, October 23, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 580)
    1. Dunkirk - Republican Headquarters 2. Dunkirk - Lunch with local leaders 3. Dunkirk - Kraft Foods Plant 4. Fredonia - State University College 5. Fredonia - Republican Headquarters 6. Jamestown - Republican Headquarters 7. Jamestown - Reception and dinner
  - New York, New York, October 24, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 581)
    1. Grand Council of Columbia Associations
  - Troy, New York; Albany, New York, October 26, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 582)
    Troy 1. Rensselaer County Republican Rally Albany 1. Albany County Republican Committee Dinner
  - New York, New York, October 27, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 583)
    1. Campaigning with Congressman John Lindsay
  - New York, New York; Glens Falls, New York, October 29, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 584)
    New York City 1. Meeting with women political leaders Glens Falls 1. Warren County Young Republicans
  - Regrets, October 1964 (Box 18, Folder 585)
    1. Columbia Republican League 2. Broome County Committee 3. Rallies in Erie and Niagara Counties 4. Tri-County Young Republican Rally 5. Pearl River Republican Club
  - Out of State Appearance Memoranda, December 1963-January 1964 (Box 18, Folder 586)
    1. Bob Douglass to Carl Spad, re: trips 2. Bob Douglass to Jack Wells, re: January invitations 3. George Hinman to Jack Wells, Louise Boyer, Bob Douglass, re: California and Oregon Dates 4. Alexander Lankler to Louise Boyer, re: New Hampshire 5. Ruth Bowen to Louise Boyer, re: transportation
  - New York, New York, November 2, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 587)
    (NAR campaigning for Senator Ken Keating) 1. Rally, Time-Life Building, Manhattan 2. Rally, 149th and 3rd, Bronx 3. Rally, Alexander's Department Store, Queens 4. Rally, Flatbush Avenue, Brooklyn 5. Rally, Abraham and Strauss, Brooklyn 6. Rally, Staten Island Ferry Terminal
  - New York, New York, November 5, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 588)
    Inauguration of Albert Bowker as Chancellor of City University of New York. NAR cancels appearance because of trip. Ronan speaks instead.
  - Rochester, New York (cancelled), November 9, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 589)
    1. Advisory Council for Advancement on Industrial Research Development
  - New York, New York; Buffalo, New York, November 16, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 590)
    New York City 1. State Traffic Safety Council Buffalo 1. Construction Industry Employers Association
  - New York, New York, November 17, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 591)
    1. Commerce and Industry Association
  - New York, New York, November 18, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 592)
    1. National Council of Chief State School Officers, reception and banquet
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 20, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 593)
    1. Presentation of "Union Pioneer Award" 2. Federal Union, Inc. banquet
  - Brooklyn, New York, November 21, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 594)
    1. Opening of Verrazano-Narrows Bridge
  - Regrets, November 1964 (Box 19, Folder 595)
    1. Africa Service Institute 2. Phi Beta Kappa Associates 3. Institute for Basic Research in Mental Retardation 4. National Urban League Equal Opportunity Day 5. Memorial to Chris Klaus Randolph Clausen 6. Planning Programs for the Hudson-Delaware Region 7. Xerox dedication ceremonies 8. Westchester County Day at the World's Fair 9. Republican National Committee Election Night 10. Larchmont Men's Club 11. Jamesville-De Witt High School Club 12. Herkimer, New York Library dedication
  - Staten Island, New York, December 2, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 596)
    1. Institute for Basic Research in Mental Retardation ground breaking
  - Denver, Colorado, December 4-5, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 597)
  - Utica, New York, December 10, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 598)
    1. Regional Development of the Adirondack-Mohawk Area 2. Film (WKTV) and radio (WIBX) interviews
  - Albany, New York, December 14, 1964; December 22, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 599)
    December 14 1. Reception for the Electoral College members December 22 1. Inauguration of State Government's Centralized Computer System 2. Luncheon and meeting with state boards 3. Legislative Correspondents Christmas Part 4. Reception at the Mansion
  - Regrets, December 1964 (Box 19, Folder 600)
    1. Jefferson County Building in Watertown 2. A. & H. Kroeger Organization 3. Taping of "Let's Find Out" 4. Testimonial Dinner for Morris W. Berinstein 5. Golden Anniversary of Kiwanis International 6. Bill of Rights Observance in Eastchester 7. Interracial Council for Business Opportunity 8. Yale Law School Address 9. National Tuberculosis Association 10. Newspaper Women's Club of New York 11. City Hall Dedication, Rye, New York 12. Stuyvesant Hall Dedication, Geneva, New York 13. Youth and Government Conference
  - Albany, New York, January 12, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 601)
  - Albany, New York, January 13, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 602)
    1. New York State Agricultural Society dinner